

#### SAMUEL OLUGBENGA JOSHUA

Agbede,llorin,Kwara state ,Nigeria +2348109076441 | samuelolugbenga97@gmail.com

in https://www.linkedin.com/in/samuel-olugbenga

## **Objective**

I am a self taught fullstack software developer focusing on svelte for front end development and laravel for backend development while communicting with the two through inertia js thus creating an higly productive and fast monolithic work environment .I'm currently seeking employment with a fast-growing startup and organizations. I bring more than four years experience writing JavaScript and more than four years experience in the technology industry.

## **Experience**

• Freelancing 2020 - Present

Svelte front end Web developer

I worked with clients to design responsive and high performance user interfaces.

I worked with clients to convert theirs designs into code and reusable components.

I worked with clients to convert their legacy codes to new and productive solutions /framework like svelte

• Freelancing 2019 - Present

Laravel backend developer

I worked with clients to design and architect their business backend logic .

Maintenance and creating scalable data structures and databases for their web application.

I help in the design of business and backend logic for their day to day web app usage

Help to create and add functionalities to their laravel admin to automate common activities

• Freelancing 2019 - Present

Front end developer

Create front end interfaces with html and css

Create dynamic interface with Javascript

I helped in the conversion of designs nd sketched to code

### Education

University of Ilorin
 MBBS
 2015 - present

AbCHS college Ilorin
 Secondary school leaving certificate

2008 -2014

#### **Personal Details**

Portfolio website: https://samoj.netlify.app/

Blog : https://samueloj.netlify.app/

Email : Samuelolugbenga97@gmail.com

# Skills

- Javascript
- Html
- Css
- Svelte
- Laravel

- Inertia js
- Git